A Finding Aid to the Frank Perls Papers and Frank Perls Gallery Records, circa 1920-1983, bulk 1949-1975, in the Archives of American Art AAA.perlfran
Archives of American Art
- Subject Files, circa 1939-1983; Series 4; (Box 6-22; 16.5 linear feet)
  - Miscellaneous Bo, 1950-1975 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Miscellaneous Br, 1950-1975 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Miscellaneous Bu-By, 1950-1975 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - B. C. Holland Gallery, 1961-1973 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Solomon Baker, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Baltimore Museum of Art, 1959-1972 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Stanley Barbee, 1950-1966 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Sidney Barlow, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Arline Barnsdall Estate, 1952-1953 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Gene Bautzer, 1958-1969 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Max Beckman, 1950, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - B. E. Bensinger, 1961-1973 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Berkeley Express and Moving Co., 1952-1962 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Betty McLean Gallery, 1951-1953, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - City of Beverly Hills Show - "50 Years of Beverly Hills,", 1964 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Michael Blankfort, 1958-1969 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Barbara Gopel, 1970-1972 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Margaret and Harry Bradley, 1952-1973 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - George Bradshaw, 1950-1967 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Leon Brillouin, 1944, 1950-1958 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - William Brinkman, 1955 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Eugene Berman, 1947-1960, 1964-1965; (3 folders) (Box 7, Folder 35-37)
  - Eugene Berman - Photographs, circa 1937-1952 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - John Berggruen, 1970-1975 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Heinz Berggruen, 1954-1975; (10 folders) (Box 8, Folder 2-11)
  - Heinz Berggruen - Financial Records, 1966-1975; (2 folders) (Box 8, Folder 12-13)
  - Heinz Berggruen - Consigned Picasso Exhibit, 1961-1962 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Heinz Berggruen - Consigned Chagall Exhibit, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Heinz Berggruen - Consigned Picasso and Matisse Exhibit, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Heinz Berggruen - Consigned Exhibition of Lithographs, Etchings, and Linoleum Cuts, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Bishop Lawsuit - Maurice Utrillo Painting, 1972-1973; (2 folders) (Box 8, Folder 18-19)
  - Leigh Block, 1957-1967 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Jean Boggs, 1956-1971 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Pierre Bonnard, circa 1952-1966 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Eugene Boudin, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Charles Boyer, 1959-1970, 1983; (2 folders) (Box 8, Folder 24-25)
  - Charles Boyer - Photographs from Perls Inventory, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Alan Brandt - Kamer Gallery, 1963-1966 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Georges Braque - Photographs of Works of Art, circa 1957-1961 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Erica Brausen - The Hanover Gallery, 1958-1974 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - William Brice, 1951-1961; (3 folders) (Box 8, Folder 30-32)
  - William Brice, 1962-1965, 1969-1975; (2 folders) (Box 9, Folder 1-2)
  - William Brice - Photographs, circa 1947-1960 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - David Bright, 1958-1964 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Dolly Bright, 1966-1981 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Dolly Bright - Inventory of Property for David Bright, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Sidney and Frances Brody, 1950-1975; (4 folders) (Box 9, Folder 7-10)
  - Sidney and Frances Brody - Insurance, circa 1967-1971; (2 folders) (Box 9, Folder 11-12)
  - Sidney and Frances Brody - Photographs, circa 1950-1975 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Heidi Bucher, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Bernard Buffet, circa 1956 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Carter Burden, 1963-1967 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Reg Butler - Exhibitions, 1963-1964, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Reg Butler - Exhibition Photographs and Catalogs, 1963-1964 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Miscellaneous Ca-Ce, 1950-1975 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Miscellaneous Ch-Cl, 1950-1975 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Miscellaneous Co-Cu, 1950-1975 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Alexander Calder, 1950-1973 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Alexander Calder - Printed Material, circa 1949-1973 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - California Palace of the Legion of Honor, 1950-1971; (2 folders) (Box 9, Folder 24-25)
  - William Candy, 1955, 1957-1973; (3 folders) (Box 9, Folder 26-28)
  - Cass Canfield, 1970, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Carnegie Institute, 1952-1967 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Cart and Crate, 1974-1976 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Paul Cezanne, 1963-1974 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Marc Chagall, 1951-1972 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Wesley Chamberlain, 1962-1963 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - City Art Museum of St. Louis, 1950-1974 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Arthur J. Cohen (Tom), 1950-1951 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Ludwig and Erik Charell, 1954-1974 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Giorgio de Chirico, circa 1972-1973 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Christie, Manson, and Wood, Inc., 1966-1974 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Robert Chuey, 1950-1963; (3 folders) (Box 10, Folder 3-5)
  - Cincinnati Art Museum, 1959 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Cincinnati Modern Art Society, 1950-1954 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - City of Paris, California, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Paul Lewis Clemons, 1941-1951 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Victoria Coberly, 1970-1973 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Coe Kerr Gallery, 1969-1975 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Sidney Cohn, 1958-1971 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Herbert Cole, 1950-1974 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - John Coleman, 1959-1961 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Colorado Springs Fine Arts Center, 1953-1955, 1965; (2 folders) (Box 10, Folder 15-16)
  - Committee to Rescue Italian Art - Auction, 1966-1967 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Barnaby Conrad, 1953-1955 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Douglas Cooper, 1960-1972 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Camille Corot, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Gustave Courbet, 1972-1973 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Leonardo Cremonini, 1952-1954 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Templeton Crocker Estate, 1959-1960, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Jerome Crossman Estate, 1970-1974 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - George Cukor, 1950-1967 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Davd Cummings, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Miscellaneous Da-De, 1950-1975 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Miscellaneous Di-Du, 1950-1975 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Abner Dean, 1955-1957 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Kirk Douglas, 1956-1969 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - B. N. Desenberg, 1966-1975 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Louis W. Douglas, Jr., 1958-1961 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Peter Deitsch, 1962-1967 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Dallas Museum of Fine Arts, 1952-1953, 1961-1967 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Dallas Museum for Contemporary Arts, 1959-1963 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Danzas and Co. International Shipping, 1960 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Lew Davis, 1950-1952 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Day and Meyer - Packers, Shippers, and Movers, 1961-1963 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - John Decker, circa 1939-1942 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Edgar Degas - Copperplates, 1959-1964, 1979; (2 folders) (Box 10, Folder 40-41)
  - Edgar Degas - Copperplates Exhibit - Photographs, 1959 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Edward Degas - Photographs of Works of Art, Undated (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Gabriel Dereppe, 1957-1964; (2 folders) (Box 10, Folder 44-45)
  - Armand Deutsch, 1951, 1955, 1959-1963, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Ross DeVean, 1952-1962 (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - John Dodds, 1971-1972 (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - The Downtown Gallery, 1949-1956, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 49-50)
  - Charles Dreifus, 1954-1966 (Box 10, Folder 51)
  - Rene Dreyfusss, 1962-1963 (Box 10, Folder 52)
  - Jean Dubuffet, 1958-1960, 1969, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 53)
  - Jean Dubuffet, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 54)
  - Jean Dubuffet, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Teeny Duchamp, circa 1960-1969 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Charles Ducommun, 1960-1974 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Raoul Dufy, 1954, 1969-1974 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Durlacher Brothers, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous E, 1950-1975 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Edwin Engelberts Galerie, 1968-1974 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Majorie Eaton, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Lynn Epsteen, 1970-1974 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Ernest Raboff Gallery, 1960-1967 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Eric Estorick, 1958-1960 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Maybelle Ekren, 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Max Ernst, circa 1961 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous Fa-Fl, 1950-1975 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Miscellaneous Fo-Fu, 1950-1975 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - William Fadiman, 1959-1969 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - George Fearing, Jr., 1953-1955 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - M. F. Feheley, 1957-1961 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Richard Feigen, 1955-1974; (2 folders) (Box 11, Folder 19-20)
  - Marianne Feilchenfeldt, 1951-1971 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Feingarten Galleries, 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Lyonel Feininger, circa 1960 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Felix Landau Gallery, 1957-1970 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Gian Ferrari, 1958-1959 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Fine Arts Gallery of San Diego, 1952-1974 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Oskar Fischinger, 1950-1962 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Lawrence Fleischman, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - William Flores, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Fogg Art Museum - Harvard University, 1962-1971 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Fort Worth Museums, 1967, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Fort Worth Art Center, 1956-1974 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Sam Francis, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Ruth Francken, 1968-1970; (3 folders) (Box 11, Folder 34-36)
  - Ruth Francken - Photographs, circa 1968-1969 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Jane Fish Franklin, 1972-1973 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Arthur Freed, 1951-1974 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Theodore Freiborg, 1960-1962 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - George Frelinghuysen, 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Frick Art Reference Library, 1950-1971 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Alan Frumkin Gallery, 1956-1970 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Miscellaneous Ga-Ge, 1950-1975 (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Miscellaneous Gi-Go, 1950-1975 (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - Miscellaneous Gr-Gu, 1950-1975 (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - Christa Gaehde, 1972-1973 (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - Galerie Beyeler, 1956-1974; (2 folders) (Box 11, Folder 48-49)
  - Galerie Beyeler - Exhitition at Frank Perls Gallery, 1966-1967; (2 folders) (Box 11, Folder 50-51)
  - Galerie Bing, 1951-1957 (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - Galerie Bonino, 1969-1970 (Box 11, Folder 53)
  - Galerie Brockstedt, 1971, 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 54)
  - Galerie Brusberg, 1967-1974 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Galerie Claude Bernard, 1963-1975 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Galerie de France, 1967-1968; (2 folders) (Box 12, Folder 3-4)
  - Galerie Europe, 1962-1968 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Galerie Georges Moos, 1969-1974; (2 folders) (Box 12, Folder 6-7)
  - Galerie Gerald Cramer, 1955-1974 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Galerie Jan Krugier, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Galerie Louise Leiris, 1953-1974 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Galerie Wolfgang Ketterer, 1960-1976; (2 folders) (Box 12, Folder 11-12)
  - Galleria Odyssia, 1958-1959 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Galerie Rosengart, 1953-1967 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Galerie Rudolf Hoffman, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Galerie St. Etienne, 1956-1957 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Galerie Schmucking, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Galerie 65, 1955-1966 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Galleria D'Arte Del Naviglio, 1958-1960 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Paul Gauguin, 1972-1973 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - General Adjustment Bureau, 1952-1954 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - German Art Dealers, 1954-1955 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Philip Gersh, 1955-1972 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Otto Gerson, 1950-1969; (2 folders) (Box 12, Folder 24-25)
  - Alberto Giacometti, circa 1959-1975; (2 folders) (Box 12, Folder 26-27)
  - Alberto Giacometti - Ink Sketch, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Alberto Giacometti - Exhibition, 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Alberto Giacometti - Photographs of Works of Art, circa 1960-1970; (2 folders) (Box 12, Folder 30-31)
  - Gimpel Fils Gallery, 1958-1961 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Harry Ginsberg, 1950-1958 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Robert Ginder, 1960-1965 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Paulette Goddard, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Jean Godebski, 1960-1961 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - William Goetz, 1947, 1951-1972 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - William Goetz - Inventory and Appraisal Sheets, circa 1959-1969 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Roy J. Goldberg Case - Clippings, 1955 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Sam and Frances Goldwyn, 1953, 1971-1974 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Gallery Loans - Closing Camden Drive Gallery, circa 1964-1965 (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Miscellaneous Ha, 1950-1975 (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Miscellaneous He-Hn, 1950-1975 (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - Miscellaneous Ho-Hy, 1950-1975 (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Walter Haas, 1950-1971; (2 folders) (Box 12, Folder 45-46)
  - Hahn Brothers, 1969-1973 (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Paul Haim, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - William Haines, 1950-1974 (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - Robert Halff, 1958-1961 (Box 12, Folder 50)
  - Hammer Galleries, 1957-1968 (Box 12, Folder 51)
  - Joan Harrison, 1960-1962 (Box 12, Folder 52)
  - Ernest Hauswedell, 1969-1974 (Box 12, Folder 53)
  - Gaston de Havenon, 1955-1971 (Box 12, Folder 54)
  - Harold Hecht, 1956-1974; (2 folders) (Box 12, Folder 55-56)
  - Joan Hazlitt, 1969-1974 (Box 12, Folder 57)
  - Catharine Heerman, 1954-1958 (Box 12, Folder 58)
  - Hein Antiquites, 1953-1971 (Box 12, Folder 59)
  - Marco Hellman, 1951-1968 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Ernest Herman, 1966-1972 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Michael Hertz, 1967-1973 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Philippe Hiquily, 1958-1962, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Joseph Hirshhorn, 1961-1975; (2 folders) (Box 13, Folder 5-6)
  - Alfred Hitchcock, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Rudolf Hoflehner, 1963-1973 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Gordon Holmes, 1955-1975 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Florence Homolka, 1950-1952 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Honolulu Academy of Arts, 1952-1961 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Arthur Hornblow, 1955-1958 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - John Houseman, 1950-1956 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Houston Museum of Fine Arts, 1951-1966 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Miscellaneous I, 1950-1975 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - I.R.S. Art Advisory Panel, 1970-1973 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Indiana University, 1959 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - The Isaac Delgado Museum, 1951, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Isaac Brothers Company, 1967-1969 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Miscellaneous Ja-Jo, 1950-1975 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Miscellaneous Jo-Ju, 1950-1975 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - J. Lee Johnson, 1953-1976 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Sam and Mildred Jaffe, 1950-1963 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - James Bourlet and Sons, Inc., 1974 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - James Vigeveno, 1949-1965 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Miscellaneous Ka-Ke, 1950-1975 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Miscellaneous Kh-Kl, 1950-1975 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Miscellaneous Ko-Ku, 1950-1975 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Estella Katzenellenbogen, 1950-1975; (2 folders) (Box 13, Folder 29-30)
  - Lyton Kistler, 1950-1955 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - John F. Kennedy, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Wassily Kandinsky, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Kimbell Art Museum, 1969-1974 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Joseph Koepfli, 1962-1975 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Edmond Kohn, 1961-1962 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Kornfeld and Klipstein, 1961-1973; (4 folders) (Box 13, Folder 37-40)
  - Ernie Kovacs, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - Karl Heinz Krause, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - Kunst Kabinett Klihm, 1954-1958 (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - Miscellaneous La, 1950-1975 (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - Miscellaneous Led-Les, 1950-1975 (Box 13, Folder 45)
  - Miscellaneous Lev-Lew, 1950-1975 (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - Miscellaneous Li, 1950-1975 (Box 13, Folder 47)
  - Miscellaneous Lo-Ly, 1950-1975 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Stephan Lackner, 1955-1963 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - La Jolla Museum of Art, 1960-1969 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Charles Laughton, 1955-1959, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Jacob Lawrence, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Rico Lebrun, 1950-1967; (3 folders) (Box 14, Folder 6-8)
  - Lucien Lefebvre-Foinet, 1963-1974 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Legal Matters, 1956-1960 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Fernand Leger, circa 1952-1958 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Leicester Galleries, 1949, 1953-1968 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Jack Lemmon, 1963-1976 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Sarah Lewis Estate, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Orme Lewis, 1959-1971 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Jacques Lipchitz, 1951-1957 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Life Magazine, 1952-1961 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Anatole Litvak, 1950-1959 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - David Loew Estate, 1966-1973 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Long Beach Municipal Art Center, 1952-1959 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Long Beach Museum of Art, 1957-1973 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Look Magazine, 1951-1953 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Los Angeles - City and County Agencies, 1950-1968; (3 folders) (Box 14, Folder 23-25)
  - Los Angeles County Museum - Art Rental Gallery, 1953-1964; (5 folders) (Box 14, Folder 26-30)
  - Los Angeles County Museum of Art, 1941-1942, 1950-1974; (5 folders) (Box 14, Folder 31-35)
  - Los Angeles County Museum of Art - Edvard Munch Exhibition, 1968-1969; (2 folders) (Box 14, Folder 36-37)
  - Los Angeles County Museum of Art - Picasso Exhibition, 1966; (2 folders) (Box 14, Folder 38-39)
  - Los Angeles County Art Museum Fund, circa 1954-1964 (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - Los Angeles Furniture Mart, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - Julius Lowy, 1951-1959 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Wright Ludington, 1950-1975 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Lumley Cazalet Ltd., 1966-1976; (8 folders) (Box 15, Folder 3-10)
  - Lumley Cazalet Ltd. - Matisse Woodblock, 1975-1976 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous Mac-Mah, 1950-1975 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous Mai-Mar, 1950-1975 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous Mas-Mey, 1950-1975 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Miscellaneous Mi-Moo, 1950-1975 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Miscellaneous Mor-My, 1950-1975 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - M. H. de Young Memorial Museum, 1950-1955 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - M. Knoedler and Company, 1949-1973; (11 folders) (Box 15, Folder 18-28)
  - M. Knoedler and Company - Telegrams, 1950-1956 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Claire McCardell, 1952-1971 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - James McClane, 1950-1972 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Jim McGarrell, 1955-1974; (4 folders) (Box 16, Folder 1-4)
  - Jim McGarrell - Exhibitions, circa 1960-1964 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Jim McGarrell - Sales, 1961-1965; (3 folders) (Box 16, Folder 6-8)
  - Jim McGarrell - Sales Invoices, 1955-1965 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Jimmy McHugh, 1951-1968, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Madoura Galerie, 1956-1962; (2 folders) (Box 16, Folder 11-12)
  - Maeght Editeur, 1950-1974 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Aristide Maillol, circa 1960 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Margaret Mallory, 1957-1965 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Martin Manulis, 1959-1967 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Frederic March, 1974-1975 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Hans Marcuse, 1953-1954 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Stanley Marcus, 1949-1973; (3 folders) (Box 16, Folder 19-21)
  - Hans Marcuse, 1955-1959 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Eugene Marich, 1954-1967; (2 folders) (Box 16, Folder 23-24)
  - Marino Marini, circa 1954-1968; (2 folders) (Box 16, Folder 25-26)
  - Luella and Sam Maslon, 1951-1970 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Gregory Masurovsky, 1969-1970; (2 folders) (Box 16, Folder 28-29)
  - Henri Matisse, circa 1964-1974 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Henri Matisse - Potential Fake Bronze, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Henri Matisse - Public Auction Catalogs, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Henri Matisse - Exhibition, 1952 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Henri Matisse - Woodblocks, circa 1965-1976 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Henri Matisse - Photographs, Undated (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Henri Matisse - Insurance Fraud, 1968-1974 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Jean Matisse, 1963-1974; (2 folders) (Box 17, Folder 2-3)
  - Pierre Matisse, 1949-1974; (8 folders) (Box 17, Folder 4-11)
  - Peter Matisse, 1960-1973 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Roberto Matta, 1960-1965, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Patrick Matthiesen, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Morton May, 1952-1971 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Tom May, 1951-1967 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Mayfair Fine Art, 1969-1971 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - The Mayor Gallery, 1965-1975 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - David Mellinkoff, 1953-1955 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Paul Mellon, 1968-1976 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1950-1968 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Thomas Miller, 1968-1974 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - The Minneapolis Institute of Arts, 1951-1970 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Harold Mirisch, 1957-1970 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Joan Miro, circa 1971-1975 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Joan Miro - "30 Graphics" Exhibition, 1969-1970 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Joan Miro - Photographs, circa 1969-1970 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Edward Mitchell, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Tom Mitchell, 1940-1965; (2 folders) (Box 17, Folder 29-30)
  - Amedeo Modigliani, 1951-1963 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Claude Monet, Undated (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Henry Moore, 1956-1958 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Giorgio Morandi, circa 1950s (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Robert Motherwell, 1951 (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Edvard Munch, circa 1972 (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - Edvard Munch - Catalog, Undated (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - Museum of Modern Art, 1950-1974; (4 folders) (Box 18, Folder 1-4)
  - Museum of Modern Art - Insurance Claim, 1970-1972 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous N, 1950-1975 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - National Gallery of Art, 1960-1973 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - National Museum of Western Art - Tokyo, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Patricia Neal, 1950-1968 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Edward Newell, 1958-1960 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Gladys Norton, 1955-1965 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous O, 1950-1975 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - L'Obelisco Galleria d'Arte, 1955-1967 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Clifford Odets Estate, 1967-1968 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Gerald Oliven, 1953-1955 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Niels Onstad, 1961-1962 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Doris Oppenheimer, 1952 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Walter Oppenheimer, 1961-1968 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Oslo, Norway, 1959-1970 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Miscellaneous Pa-Pe, 1950-1975 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Miscellaneous Pe-Ph, 1950-1975 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Miscellaneous Pl-Po, 1950-1975 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Miscellaneous Pr-Pu, 1950-1975 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Louis Pappas, 1951-1968; (2 folders) (Box 18, Folder 24-25)
  - Parke-Bernet Galleries, 1950-1972; (3 folders) (Box 18, Folder 26-28)
  - Pasadena Art Museum, 1954-1973 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Jules Pascin, circa 1962, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Peter Paul, 1972-1980; (2 folders) (Box 18, Folder 31-32)
  - Paul Kantor Gallery, 1957-1974; (2 folders) (Box 18, Folder 33-34)
  - Channing Peake, 1950-1962; (2 folders) (Box 18, Folder 35-36)
  - Katie Peake, 1950, 1971-1972 (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - Max Pechstein, 1956-1958 (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - Hugo Perls, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - Klaus Perls, 1950-1953 (Box 18, Folder 40)
  - Klaus Perls, 1954-1975; (5 folders) (Box 19, Folder 1-5)
  - Marianne Perls, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Eugenie Soderberg, circa 1971 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Phoenix Art Galleries and Museums, 1953-1964 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Pablo Picasso - Printed Materials, circa 1939-1973 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Pablo Picasso - Photographs of Works of Art, 1922-1973; (2 folders) (Box 19, Folder 10-11)
  - Pablo Picasso - Photographs of Family and Friends, circa 1950-1970; (2 folders) (Box 19, Folder 12-13)
  - Pablo Picasso - Photographs of "Picasso Girl,", circa 1950-1960 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Pablo Picasso - Verifications of Work, circa 1948-1963 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Pablo Picasso - Correspondence, circa 1953-1973 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Maya Widmaier (Picasso), 1967-1976 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Maya Widmaier (Picasso) with Frank Perls - Photographs, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - James Pinto, 1952 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Camille Pissarro, Undated (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - James Poe, 1950-1963 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - James Pollock, 1950-1958 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Vincent Price, 1952-1968 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - The Print Collectors Newsletter, 1971-1974 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Quatre Chemins - Editart, 1952-1974 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Miscellaneous Ra, 1950-1975 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Miscellaneous Re, 1950-1975 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Miscellaneous Rh-Ri, 1950-1975 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Miscellaneous Ro, 1950-1975 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Miscellaneous Ru-Ry, 1950-1975 (Box 19, Folder 30)